Mc Allain S. Casindad



career.mcallain@gmail.com



Q 09703361309/09922192332



linkedin.com/in/mc-allain-casindad



https://mc-allain.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary

I am a fast-learner, detail-oriented and dedicated programmer/developer. I always lead my team in project development and able to develop websites and applications by myself. I have 6 years of experience in Computer Programming and learned many programming languages and tools in different platforms such as Web, Mobile and Desktop. In my previous work as a Mobile and Web Developer Intern, I developed 2 Mobile Applications and a Website in just span of 3 months in which I am the lead and primary contributor.

Experience



Mobile Developer

Mobile Palengke Jun 2022 - Aug 2022 (3 months)

Information Technology Representative/Management Advisor

Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc. Jul 2022 - Aug 2022 (2 months)

Development Team Leader

Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc. Jul 2022 - Aug 2022 (2 months)

Full-stack Developer

Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc. Jun 2022 - Aug 2022 (3 months)

Mobile Developer

Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc. Jun 2022 - Aug 2022 (3 months)

Freelance Software Developer

Freelance Aug 2017 - Jun 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Education



Lyceum of Alabang

Senior High School, Information and Communications Technology 2016 - 2018

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology Jun 2018 - Sep 2022

Skills

Leadership • Management • Software Development • Web Development • Mobile Application

Development • Analytical Skills • Problem Solving • Critical Thinking • Communication • Evaluations

Honors & Awards

3 Night Owl Awards - Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc.

Aug 2022

Dedicated to their tasks even after working hours.

Night Owl Award - Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc.

Jul 2022

Dedicated to their tasks even after working hours.

- IT Intern of the Month Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc.
 Aug 2022
- Hustler Award Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc.

 Aug 2022

The Intern accomplished numerous tasks with the highest quality of performance.

Hustler Award - Wedding Suppliers Association of the Philippines Inc.
Jul 2022

The Intern accomplished numerous tasks with the highest quality of performance.

Most Innovative Capstone Project - Lyceum of Alabang

Mar 2018

The Development of Computerized Voting System for the Senior High School Student Council in Lyceum of Alabang using Visual Basic.NET

Best in Computer Programming - Lyceum of Alabang
Mar 2018

Most Outstanding Work Immersion Trainee - Lyceum of Alabang
Mar 2018

The one and only awardee in Information and Communications Technology Strand of Batch 2018